frotcom.com 2019-07-11

# Privacy policy - Frotcom

At Frotcom International, we collect, process, store and use personal data that is necessary to comply with contracts and legal obligations arising from our business activity, as well as to send information about our products, and to provide excellent service to our customers.

  Personal data is stored for as long as the relationship with Frotcom International lasts and for the legally required period, and is transferred to the entities that the Law requires or to referenced partners, which in this case, is with the data owner's consent.

  Personal data processing is done according to the proper practices to ensure information security, integrity, confidentiality and availability. Frotcom International employees ensure high ethical, confidentiality and secrecy standards, in accordance with the company's values and rules, as described in the quality manual and the human resources policy.

  We ensure compliance with legislation in force on data protection and privacy, having configured our processes to provide efficient replies to requests for access and consultation of personal data, as well as updates, changes, or delivery of data in a common and structured format, if applicable.

  You may request to have your data removed, restrict and object to data processing and automatic processing of personal data for profiling, as well as data portability, in the case of requests in compliance with current legislation. Owners of personal data can file a complaint on its processing with the national supervisory authority, the National Commission for Data Protection (CNPD - Comissão Nacional de Proteção de Dados).

  For additional information, clarifications or complaints regarding personal data processing, please contact: [dataprivacy@frotcom.com](mailto:dataprivacy@frotcom.com).
